<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MakeUp</string>
    <string name="bridal_makeup">
From the blending foundation to lipstick that lasts all day, we got step-by-step beauty tips to help you make the most of your make up:

        \n\nStep:1: Moisturizer
Use a cleat cotton Swap to scoop out a small amount, warm it up in your hands and the press it into your face. Massage it for 30 seconds, don’t forget your neck and the tips of your eye brow.
        \n\nStep 2: Primer
Gives longevity for your foundation warm up a dime-sized amount that massage it int the face, cover entire face with it and bring it down the neck to soften the appearance t of the skin

        \n\nStep 3: Foundation
Squirt some onto your hand warm it up and blend it in using your tongue or sponge. Then using the dry side of the sponge, butt the into your face.

        \n\nStep 4: Concealer
Get two shades of concealer – a lighter one and a darker one and blend them together on the back of your hand with a brush to get a custom camouflage colour. Test the shades on your chin first gently brush a bit of concealer onto the area where you need it and the press it in with your finger continue until the area is covered.

        \n\nStep 5: Powder
Using a puff over a powder bush to apply the powder on face, blend it very well the to your desire task.

        \n\nStep 6: Eye shadow
Apply your favourite eye shadow, you can mix different colour together.

        \n\nStep 7: Eye line
Apply eye liner to sharpen your eye shadow

        \n\nStep 8: Mascara
Apply mascara to your lashes to make them look perfect.

        \n\nStep 9: Lipstick
Apply any lipstick of your choice, blend the side of your mouth with concede.

        \n\nStep 10: blush
Apply blush to give you that amazing good of a grid.
    </string>
    <string name="everyday_makeup">
        Step 1: foundation
Squeeze some on to your hand warm it up and blend it in using your finger or a sponge.

        \n\nStep 2: Eye brow
Draw any shape of eye brow, and conceal it with your conceal

        \n\nStep 3: Powder
Proceed to applying your powder with a puff over powder brush

        \n\nStep 4: eyeshadow
Put on a simple light eye shadow

        \n\nStep 5: Eyeline
Apply eyeline to shapen your eye shadow

        \n\nStep 6: Mascara
Mascarize your eyelashes to look perfect

        \n\nStep 7: lip gloss
apply a light lipgloss to your lip -> perfct everyday makeup


    </string>

    <string name="party_makeup">

        step 1: Foundation
apply your foundation using your finger or sponge

        \n\nstep 2: eyebrow
draw your eye brow  and conceal it with concealer

        \n\nstep 3: powder
apply your powder with a puff of powder brush


    </string>
    <string name="carnival_makeup">

        Step 1: primer or foundation
Always use a primer before applying makeup, primer provide a smooth base for makeup.

        \n\nStep 2: eye lashes
Use spirit gum to apply your gems but not to stick your lashes

        \n\nStep 3: liquia line
Apply liquid line beneath your black lashes or colour lashes to keep lashes to keep lashes or longer

        \n\nStep 4: powder
Use a layering technique with your powder and some fix, it spray to keep your look fresh all day long

        \n\nStep 5:
Lipstick line you lips and fill in lips with linene.

    </string>
</resources>
